{
    "subject": "resource/Pierre-Gilles_de_Gennes",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/\u00c9cole_Normale_Sup\u00e9rieure",
    "human_readable": "Pierre-Gilles de Gennes attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.985734224319458,
            "question": "Was Pierre-Gilles de Gennes a student at \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9850334525108337,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Pierre-Gilles de Gennes and \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9540167450904846,
            "question": "What are some notable alumni of \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure besides Pierre-Gilles de Gennes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.940552294254303,
            "question": "Name a notable person who attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6815944314002991,
            "question": "What fields of study are typically offered at \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.659224271774292,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the history of \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6488098502159119,
            "question": "What institution was Pierre-Gilles de Gennes affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6233903169631958,
            "question": "What type of school is \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5920262932777405,
            "question": "Who were some influential professors at \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5709055066108704,
            "question": "Where did Pierre-Gilles de Gennes study?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pierre-Gilles de Gennes attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7170_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some influential professors at \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7170_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of school is \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7170_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What institution was Pierre-Gilles de Gennes affiliated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7170_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7170_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that Pierre Gilles de Gennes studied at the Ecole Normale Superieure, and later became a research engineer at the Atomic Research Centre, which was located in Paris, where he also received his doctorate."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that Pierre Gilles de Gennes was schooled at home until he was 12 years old and then went on to study at the \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure, from which he graduated in 1955. Therefore, the statement that Pierre-Gilles de Gennes attended \u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}